(Dan:)vicious little Bernadette.
(Penny:)Come on. She's not that bad.
(Dan:)Oh, yeah?
(Dan:)At the company picnic
she yelled at me and my grandson
(Dan:)for losing
the three-legged race.
I mean, he still calls her "that
mean kid with the big boobies."
(Penny:)I know she can be
a little intense, but, I swear,
(Penny:)she is so sweet
once you get past all the...
Hey,
(Bernadette:)what are you
talking about?
(Penny:)Oh. We were just talking
(Penny:)about how much we love working
with you. Isn't that right?
(Penny:)Dan?
(Sheldon:)Over the years here
at Fun With Flags,
(Sheldon:)we've had an opportunity to
learn, laugh, wonder...
(Amy:)And, yes, even shed
a tear or two.
(Sheldon:)Like when you do a two-hour
Fourth of July spectacular
(Sheldon:)and it doesn't
get recorded.
(Amy:)How many times do I have
to say I'm sorry?
How about 4,000.
(Sheldon:)One for every domino I set up
to make that American flag.
(Sheldon:)Please enjoy
these highlights.